<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--Generated by www.mi2ar.com-->
<resources>
  <string name="action_help">المساعدة</string>
  <string name="app_name">تحميل توربو</string>
  <string name="conn_charging_warning">قد يؤدي رسوم إضافية تبعاً لتحميله عبر شبكات الهاتف المحمول.</string>
  <string name="conn_notice_detail">تمكين \"تحميل توربو\"، يجب تشغيل الـ Wi-Fi والبيانات المتنقلة.</string>
  <string name="conn_notice_title">أما المحمول أو الشبكة المحلية اللاسلكية هو OFF.</string>
  <string name="connection_mobile">البيانات المتنقلة</string>
  <string name="connection_wlan">WLAN</string>
  <string name="enable_switch_off">إيقاف تشغيل</string>
  <string name="enable_switch_on">تشغيل</string>
  <string name="hetcomm_help">&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Turbo Download Help&lt;/u&gt; &lt;/h1&gt;<br>Download large files at top speed by using WLAN and 4G/3G at the same time. &lt;h4&gt;1. Go to Settings and tap Turbo Download.&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;h4&gt;2. Tap the switch to turn on Turbo Download.&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;<b>[Tip]</b> To speed up download if connected to both WLAN and 4G/3G at the start of your download. &lt;p&gt;<b>[Tip]</b> If your WLAN or 4G/3G connection is too slow, you can use your faster network connection to download. &lt;p&gt;<b>[Tip]</b> Speed and performance of Turbo Download may be affected network environment while downloading. <br>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- If the signals are unstable, the speed and performance of this feature may be affected. <br>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- however, on the average, download speed will be doubled than compared to using only WLAN or 4G/3G alone. &lt;p&gt;<b>[Tip]</b> When the speed difference of WLAN and 4G/3G is large(Normally 2.5 times), the Turbo Download will stop or will not support to avoid getting bad performance with regard to speed. &lt;p&gt;<b>[Tip]</b> The Turbo Download would be disabled automatically once Tethering/Vpn is turned on. &lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="hetcomm_intro">تحميل ملفات كبيرة (أكثر من 20 ميغابايت) أسرع باستخدام شبكات WLAN و 4 ز 3 ز في الوقت نفسه. سيظهر رمز \"تحميل توربو\" في شريط المعلومات عندما يكون قيد التشغيل. استخدام \"توربو تحميل\"، يجب تشغيل الـ Wi-Fi والبيانات المتنقلة. عندما يتم تمكين، وأي بيانات التطبيق التي الخاص بك بتحديد التحميل عبر الشبكة المحلية اللاسلكية فقط سيتم تحميلها عن طريق شبكات WLAN و 4 ز 3 ز على أي حال.</string>
  <string name="hotknotbeam_saved_location">beam</string>
  <string name="network_Mobile">3/4G</string>
  <string name="network_WiFi">WLAN</string>
  <string name="notify_top_title">Download Accelerator</string>
  <string name="ratio_is_back">توربو تنزيل إعادة استخدام الشبكات المحلية اللاسلكية والنقالة البيانات معا لتحميل الملفات.</string>
  <string name="ratio_is_single">البيانات WLAN الجوال بسرعة بطيئة. لتسريع التحميل، سوف تستخدم توربو تحميل فقط البيانات/الـ Wi-Fi المتنقلة لتحميل الملفات.</string>
  <string name="turn_off_due_to_roaming">تحميل توربو هو إيقاف التشغيل بسبب التجوال</string>
  <string name="turn_off_due_to_shutdown">تحميل توربو هو إيقاف التشغيل بسبب إيقاف التشغيل</string>
  <string name="turn_off_due_to_tether">تحميل توربو هو إيقاف التشغيل بسبب على الربط</string>
  <string name="turn_off_due_to_vpn">تحميل توربو إيقاف التشغيل بسبب Vpn</string>
  <string name="turn_on">قم بتشغيل %1$s</string>
  <string name="unit_Mbps">Mbps</string>
</resources>
